I'm honored to be here on the Iridescence Tour stage!
Parıldayan Turnenin sahnesinde olmak benim için büyük bir onur!
Alright, without further ado, I'm Xinyan, this is Hu Tao...
Lafı daha fazla uzatmayayım, Ben Xinyan, bu da Hu Tao...
And this is a li'l something called:
Ve bu da minik şey:
"The Blaze Lilies!"
"Parlak Zambak!"
I'm up here blazin' trails through the midnight sky, lightin' up the world below
Geceleri gökyüzünü parlatırım ve aşağıdaki dünyayı aydınlatırım.
And when the crowds all hear my voice, they'll meet the spirit of rock n' roll
Ve kalabalıklar sesimi duyduklarında, rock 'n' roll ruhuyla tanışacaklar.
Let's go! / Hey you, butterfly / You too, buzzin' by / Guidin' your way / To the afterlife
Hadi gidelim! Hey kelebek, sen de uç git. Ölüme giden yolda git.
Openin' the path without a fright / Oh!
Korkusuzca tüm yolları aç!
I'll light the fire / Watch it blaze / 'cross the universe
Ateşi yakıp alevleri izleyeceğim ve evreni dolaşacağım.
I'll spit my rhymes / Watch your step / Or you'll get burned
Ben şiirlerimi söylerken, sen de adımlarına dikkat et yoksa yanarsın.
Does anyone have any plans tomorrow?
Yarın için herhangi bir planı olan var mı?
With another year behind us, I think we deserve a celebration of our own
Bir yılı daha geride bırakırken bir kutlamayı hak ettiğimizi düşünüyorum.
My treat, interested?
Her şey benden, katılanlar?
The Tianquan footing the bill? I can't miss out on that
Hesap Tianquan'dan mı? O zaman ben kaçırmam bunu.
Master, Master! Listen!
Usta, Usta! Dinle!
May the year ahead be a blessed one
Önümüzdeki yıl güzel bir yıl olsun.
I believe it shall be
Eminim ki öyle olacaktır.
Master, the Xiao Lanterns... I...
Usta, Xiao Fenerleri... Ben...
Ha!
Ha!
Elementary
Sade Fenerler,
One shall fashion for you a Xiao Lantern the likes of which the world has never seen
sizin için dünyada eşi benzeri görülmemiş bir Xiao Feneri yapılacak.
Then, you must take it to Liyue Harbor, to display its magnificence for all
Sonrasında ise fenerin ihtişamını herkese göstermek için
Listen! That must be Madame Ping!
Dinle! Bu Madam Ping olmalı!